makemeold.com 2010-08-26

# Make Me Old

## Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY Make Me Old, and each of its related web sites ("Make Me Old.com") Privacy Policy Last updated October 11, 2009. 

This Privacy Policy outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of information collected via this Website. Make Me Old provides this Privacy Policy to help users make an informed decision as to whether to use or continue using the Website. 

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. Make Me Old DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO Make Me Old OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. 

This Privacy Policy applies to Make Me Old's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Make Me Old on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Website"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Make Me Old's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. Make Me Old is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third web sites or applications. By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Website Terms of Use. Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide via the Website or through other official Make Me Old contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use and/or other stated policies. 

1\. Collection of Information.

1.1 Survey Information. Make Me Old collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes an Make Me Old survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Website, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, Make Me Old or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to Make Me Old, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). Make Me Old may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this Web Site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Make Me Old or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from Make Me Old or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to Make Me Old. 

1.2 Third Party List Information. Make Me Old collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a Third Party and Make Me Old subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the Third Party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), SMS messaging details (e.g. date, time and content of the SMS message), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Make Me Old seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Make Me Old and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list. 

1.3 Other Information. Other occasions when Make Me Old obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by Make Me Old or by a Third Party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through Make Me Old's customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a Make Me Old service or newsletter (together, "Other Information"). 

1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. Make Me Old currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, Make Me Old may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information"). (a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows Make Me Old to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in Make Me Old's database. You may read more about cookies at [http://cookiecentral.com](http://cookiecentral.com/). Individuals who use the Website need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Website. (b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an img src="x" programming function -- see http://truste.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Make Me Old to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, Make Me Old might place, with the consent of a Third Party website, a web beacon on the Third Party's website where baseball products are sold. When Joe, an individual listed in Make Me Old's database, visits the fishing website, Make Me Old receives notice by means of the web beacon that Joe visited the baseball site, and Make Me Old would then update Joe's profile with the information that Joe is interested in baseball. Make Me Old may thereafter present offers of baseball related products and services to Joe. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Make Me Old also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Make Me Old's database. (c) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is Make Me Old's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, Make Me Old strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology. 

1.5 Outside Information. Make Me Old may receive information about individuals from Third Parties or from other sources of information outside of Make Me Old including information located in public databases ("Outside Information"). 

1.6 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information Make Me Old gathers or receives about individuals such as usage data, file transfer and viewing data. 

1.7 No Information Collected from Children. Make Me Old will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Make Me Old obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, Make Me Old has no such information to use or to disclose to Third Parties. Make Me Old has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). 1.8 Log File Information. When users log-in to access their account, our servers may automatically record and archive certain information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a Website. These server logs may include information vital to validating the user's authorization to access the account. Information, such as a web request, Internet Protocol (the "IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize a user's entry and activity on the Website. 1.9 Credit Card Information. Make Me Old may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Make Me Old. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Make Me Old, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Make Me Old will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to Third Parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. 

2\. Use of Individual Information.

2.1 Discretion to Use Information. THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Make Me Old currently uses Individual Information, but Make Me Old may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted, Make Me Old may update this policy from time to time. Make Me Old may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses. 

2.2 Email. Make Me Old uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Make Me Old may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Make Me Old's email lists, a person must send an email to [ecare.legal@gmail.com](mailto:ecare.legal@gmail.com). 2.2(a) Content of Email Messages. In certain commercial email messages sent by Make Me Old, an advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Make Me Old. The "Subject:" line of Make Me Old email messages will usually contain a line provided from the advertiser to Make Me Old. 2.2(b) Solicited Email. Make Me Old only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Website to receive email from Make Me Old or to individuals who have agreed on Third Party websites to receive email from Third Parties such as Make Me Old. Make Me Old does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Make Me Old's email messages. 

2.3 Targeted Advertising. Make Me Old uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Make Me Old uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.5 below) to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Make Me Old attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Make Me Old may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers. 

2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing. Make Me Old uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. 

2.5 Mobile Phone SMS Messaging. In certain cases, when requested by an individual, a Third Party may use Individual Information to provide customized content and advertising via SMS messaging to an individual's cell phone. Make Me Old is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Third Parties. 

2.6 Use of Technology Information. Make Me Old uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Make Me Old's web sites are most frequently visited. This information helps Make Me Old to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Make Me Old can target advertising and promotions to them. 

2.7 Profiles of Individuals. Make Me Old uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases. 

2.8 Storage of Individual Information. Make Me Old stores the Individual Information in a database on Make Me Old computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Make Me Old's control. Not withstanding such measures, Make Me Old cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Make Me Old computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered. 

3\. Dissemination of Individual Information.

3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties. Make Me Old MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN Make Me Old'S SOLE DISCRETION. 

3.2 Order Fulfillment. Make Me Old will transfer Individual Information to Third Parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such Third Party while using Make Me Old web sites or when responding to offers provided by Make Me Old. 

3.3 Legal Process. Make Me Old may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes. 

3.4 Summary Data. Make Me Old may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 

3.5 Access. Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting [ecare.legal@gmail.com](mailto:ecare.legal@gmail.com). Make Me Old may also grant advertising clients and email services providers' access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected. 

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Website and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Make Me Old does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and Make Me Old has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

4.2 Links. The Website and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of Third Parties. Make Me Old is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by Third Parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Make Me Old does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such Third Party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

4.3 Affiliated Companies. Make Me Old may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with Make Me Old in Make Me Old's discretion. Should Make Me Old be subject to an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of control or business entity status, Make Me Old reserves the right to transfer or assign the Information collected from the Website. 

5.Individuals Outside of the United States. Anyone using the Website outside of the United States acknowledges that personal information will be collected and stored by Make Me Old in the United States. By using the Website, you consent to the transfer of information to and/or storage of information outside of your country and in the United States. 

6\. Unsubscribe Procedures.

6.1 If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from Make Me Old, you have several options: 

1\. Unsubscribe from one email list. To unsubscribe from a particular list, either (1) send an email to [ecare.legal@gmail.com](mailto:ecare.legal@gmail.com) or (2) follow the instructions in each promotional email message sent by Make Me Old. 

2\. Unsubscribe from all of Make Me Old's email lists. We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by Make Me Old. To globally unsubscribe from all of Make Me Old's lists, send an email to [ecare.legal@gmail.com](mailto:ecare.legal@gmail.com). 

1\. Unsubscribe from a particular SMS messaging campaign. To unsubscribe from a particular SMS messaging campaign on a cell phone, send "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS message received by the individual. In addition, other methods to unsubscribe may be set forth on the website at which the individual signed up for the SMS messaging campaign. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://ftc.gov](http://ftc.gov/). If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at [ecare.legal@gmail.com](mailto:ecare.legal@gmail.com). 

California User Consumer Rights. In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov).
